You guys must be grinning on the inside when you get asked these questions.
The feel-good question grand prix
This is a little scary, but let me just tell you what kind of project it is.
We do a lot of interviews, don't we?
Are there any questions that you are happy to be asked?
Yes, there are.
Certainly. There are questions that I think I would be pretty good at if I were asked those questions, and questions that I think would get to the right point.
They keep coming up.
There are questions that make me smile when I get them.
I would like to reveal them to everyone.
I can't expose them, I can't expose them.
I've been exposed myself, but I'm a little impatient.
I'm honest.
I'm being honest.
Yes, I am.
Pretty for you.
I want to make it happen with you.
I'm a girl of mine
Tell me now, you mean?
If you don't have the words, I don't want them anymore
It's up now, it's up now
You and me, so good night
Okay, I'm going to ask you all a question now
I want everyone to think of a question that will make you grin on the inside
Will you remember it?
Hmmm, that's a tough one.
I wonder.
Yes, so, first of all, Moeka, right?
Yo! Top batter! Top batter every time, every time!
Brother on batter! Ordinary batter!
It was a simple video.
Nice words. Simple images.
That's what we're going with today.
Yes, okay.
I would like to think of a question that would make Moka grin because she would not be asked it,
Please think of a question that would make you grin if you were asked it.
Yes, I am.
I guess it's a question of whether it fits.
Right away.
I think everyone can understand this.
Really? Really?
I'm a simple guy.
I make things simple.
Simple, but actually...
Actually!
Actually, let's say "actually".
I mean, if you asked me this question, I'd have a hard time.
What? I wonder.
It's a question that's hard to deal with.
It's a question.
It's not so much a question, it's more like when four of us are interviewed and we are waiting for our turn to be interviewed, we often lose track of what questions we are asked,
Maybe that's it.
I was the fourth person to be asked a question, and when I was the first or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth or the fourth. I think about what question I'm being asked and what everyone is answering.
You said that the other day.
Yes, that's right.
I'm sorry.
What was the question?
That's right.
You've been taking it pretty slowly.
I asked you a question at all.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Everyone is a little different.
Yuzu seemed confident, so I'll start with Yuzu.
Let's start with Yuzu.
Your social networking photos are very cute.
I can't say the right answer yet.
What is the right way to put it?
Then what is the right answer?
I don't know, but Moeka wants to do her best on Instagram,
She wants to take cute pictures,
That's why I used to ask various members how to take pictures,
I used to ask the staff how to take pictures, and I would ask the staff how to take cute pictures.
I asked the staff how to take cute pictures,
I'm happy.
I'm happy, I'm happy.
I take a lot of pictures.
I'm uploading videos now.
I want to be exposed.
Okay, can I go next?
Okay, next, Aira.
I'll go this way.
There you go.
I think you've become very sophisticated recently.
I'm glad.
I wonder if the members are doing their makeup or something,
Moka, can you get any more sophisticated?
Yesterday.
Yesterday?
They were talking about how they wanted to be more sophisticated,
I've been wondering if I can't do it any more,
So I thought it would be timely and happy to hear her say this.
I see.
You should take a look at the recent days.
I wonder if they would start talking about makeup, since that's the genre they've been working hard on.
That's nice.
You write about how she's become more sophisticated recently, but it seems like she was a potato just a little while ago.
No, I'm a potato.
What?
Clearly.
No, it's a potato no matter how you look at it.
But I saw a recent model with black hair on TikTok today, maybe in the morning.
The one with the most recent black hair.
But when I look at it now, it's totally different.
Is it a lie?
But I'm happy.
I was a potato when I was CBJr.
Yes, three potatoes.
It's not a potato, it's a rice cake.
It's a rice cake.
I don't know, even the other day, they're saying chuckily buried potatoes and all kinds of things.
What do you think? To Toshimitsu-san.
Is he saying that? I don't know who said that.
Oh, no, I don't know who said that.
Oh, no.
No, it's not.
The youngest was the youngest and said it.
In the dirt, carved out of a potato.
Are you a helmet, too?
I'm a gray-haired zitama.
I have a black neck.
It's the helmet you wear when digging for potatoes.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's nice to hear you say that.
Indeed.
Then, please give us your answer, Kojima-san.
Yes, I do.
Who among the members is the most bruised and battered?
What do you mean?
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, you mean like talkative?
Yes, yes, yes.
I see. I see.
I don't know, I feel like I'm a bit of an azatayi,
I'm often blamed by the members.
That's true.
But there is the matter of the bread and so on,
Yeah, you've been getting that a lot lately.
Yes, I've been getting that a lot lately.
But from Moeka's point of view,
You think yuzu is the best, don't you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I see.
Yeah, I'm going to argue with you about that,
Sure.
You argue a lot,
Ah.
I thought it would be the opposite.
There's no way Moka would come with that idea.
Think about it.
Huh?
Yes.
Is there a question that made you grin the most?
Triangle.
Triangle? No, it's not.
It's a triangle.
Doesn't it match with Moeka?
It's a little bit right.
It fits a little.
It fits.
The question that makes me smile is. Please tell us how you do your makeup. I'd like to know how Lila does hers.
Lila.
You said it earlier, you're going to talk about makeup.
I think I have the least make-up skills and knowledge about make-up among the three of us,
That's why I think that if someone asked me to teach them because I like your makeup, I would smile and talk about it.
So you are particular about your makeup.
I'd like to hear about it.
Is it something you're particular about?
Yes, I do.
Drawing eyeliner neatly.
How do you draw it beautifully?
Is the point to make it swell up or down?
I make it swell up or down, depending on the occasion.
How do you make sure to draw beautifully?
I pull with a very steady hand, and when it clatters, I take it out with a cotton swab.
Every sound.
Mouth to mouth.
It's like this.
Yes.
And, you know, put some lame on this area.
Wow, well, the other members of Atsurashi.
I met them for the first time recently.
Oh, there's a girl who's doing it before me.
Oh, a member of No Dame Dalashi.
I was hoping I wouldn't have to do it after doing it recently.
I'm not a member of "Atsurashi de Unno".
Oh no!
But I'm curious about this, so maybe you should write an article about it.
I'd love to see a reporter write about it sometime.
I'd love it if you and your fans would follow me this year.
I'll force myself to answer your questions.
I can't give you a solid answer.
I'll have a decent answer.
I have a decent answer.
I can respond to your passion separately.
I see.
Sorry, can I always?
Who is the shallowest member of the group?
Yuzu.
Thank you.
Why?
I don't know.
Only the one who talks the most can speak first.
I don't think I'll be the first one to speak.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
You're right, Moe-face.
Moe face
speaks on the prarator
Yes, I do
By yourself
Moe face
I don't have it.
I don't think so.